offer18.com 2019-06-25

# Terms - Offer18

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes how we use and to whom we disclose personal data that is collected by us or provided by you when you visit our website located at www.offer18.com (the “Website”) or use our services (the «Services»). You will also find below the important information about your rights in relation to your personal data, so please read the policy carefully. Offer18 (“Offer18”, “us”, or “we”) acts as controller of your personal data. email privacy@offer18.com. By accessing the Website or using our Services, you become subject to this Policy. Your acceptance of the terms of this Policy, in their entirety, shall be effective to your employees, if any. 

###### How Do Clients Collect User Information Using Offer18

At the direction of our clients, who act as data controllers, Offer18 collects the following types of information from Users to help clients optimize and measure their advertising network, affiliate and publisher relationships:   
Ad Identifiers  
IP address  
Cookies  
Pixel Tags  
Imprecise Geographic Location Data derived from IP address and/or wifi networks. 

###### What information we collect and how we use it

“Personal Data” is any information relating to natural person, who can be identified directly or indirectly.   
We collect the following Personal Data about you : 

###### Information we use to provide services

Contact Information. When you register / sign up for the Services, we may collect certain contact information from you, such as your first and last name, organization name, city, state and zip code, email address, and phone number or other similar contact details to help you with your experience. Billing Information. When purchasing Services, you will be required to provide additional information that may include a credit card number or other banking or payment information. This information is required by us to verify your identity, to establish your company’s account, and set up your Services. Service Information. In order to provide Services to you and to improve our Services, we may collect information that is created or provided by you in connection with your use of the Services, including order information, chat logs, email logs and information about your actions in various client areas on the Website. We will use your Contact Information and Billing Information to provide Services and to provide you with access to the Services you have ordered, as well as support services, technical updates or updates on changes in our usage policies. The legal basis for us to use your Contact Information, Billing Information and Service Information is the agreements you enter into with us in connection with the Services (the “Services Terms”). 

###### Use of information for direct marketing

We may also use your name, email to send you company updates and marketing offers about Services you use or similar services which we provide. You object to such processing and may refuse from receiving such communication by pressing unsubscribe at the end of the sending an email to us. 

###### Browsing Information and Cookies

“Cookies” are small files that the Website or its service provider transfers (if you allow) to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser that enables the Website’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.   
We may use Cookies, web beacons and other technical means to collect and analyze certain information about how you and other visitors use the Website. This technical information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser information, and the preceding and succeeding websites you have visited, among other things. We may also keep a record of which pages of the Website you visit, and how long you spend on each page. Cookies can also be used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current Website activity, which enables us to provide you with improved Services. We also use Cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better Website experiences and tools in the future. We use Google Analytics for collecting website browsing statistics.   
We use Local Storage (HTML5), and our third party utility partner uses Local Shared Objects (Flash cookies) and Local Storage (HTML5) to store content information and preferences, and to display advertising based on your web browsing activity. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.   
You may set your browser to notify you or decline the receipt of Cookies; however, certain features of our Website or Services may not function properly or be available if your browser is configured to disable Cookies.   
Legal basis for use of cookies and other information stored on your devices is your consent, which you may freely refuse to give. To learn more about our cookie policy, please visit https://offer18.com/cookie_policy 

###### Tracking systems on our Website : 

###### Facebook Social Plugins

This website uses social plugins (“plugins”) from the social network facebook.com which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). The plugins are identified by one of the Facebook logos or the amendment “Facebook social plugin”. The list and the look of the Facebook social plugins can be viewed here: https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/. If you access a page on our website that includes such a social plugin, your browser sets up a direct connection to the Facebook servers. Facebook transfers the social plugin’s content directly to your browser which will then integrate it into the website. Therefore we have no influence on the extent of the data that Facebook collects via its social plugins, and thus, can only inform you based on our state of knowledge: Through integration of the plugin, Facebook obtains the information that you have accessed the respective page on our website, even if you are not a registered user of Facebook or are not logged into Facebook. This information as well as your browser’s IP address is transferred to Facebook’s server in the United States and is being stored there. According to Facebook, only anonymized IP addresses are stored from non-registered users in Germany. If you are logged in to Facebook, Facebook can allocate the visit to our website to your Facebook account. Facebook receives such information irrespective of whether you interact with the social plugins or not. If you do interact with the social plugins, e.g. by using the «Like-it-Button» or by posting a commentary, your browser will transfer such information directly to Facebook where it is being stored. Such information will also be published on Facebook and be displayed to your Facebook friends. For information on the purpose and extent of data collection, the further processing and use of such data by Facebook, as well as your rights in this regard and your setting options for the protection of your privacy, please refer to Facebook’s privacy policy: http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to collect data on you via our website and to combine such data with your Facebook membership data, you need to log off from Facebook before accessing our website. Furthermore, you may also block social plugins by downloading and installing add-ons for your browser, such as the Facebook blocker: http://webgraph.com/resources/facebookblocker/   
Facebook GDPR Compliance : https://www.facebook.com/business/news/facebooks-commitment-to-data-protection-and-privacy-in-compliance-with-the-gdpr 

###### Google AdWords

We as a Google AdWords customer also use Google Conversion Tracking, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google AdWords places a cookie in your browser (“Conversion Cookie”) if you have accessed our website via a Google ad. These cookies are valid for 30 days. If you access some of our sites and the cookie is still valid, we and Google can recognize that somebody has clicked on the ad and thereafter was transferred to our website. Every AdWords customers uses a different cookie, and therefore it is not possible to track cookies via the websites of AdWords customers. The information obtained via the Conversion Cookie is used in order to assemble conversion reports for AdWords customers. The AdWords customers receive the number of users that have clicked on their ad and have been transferred to a site that includes the Conversion Tracking Tag but they do not receive any information that would allow them to identify the user. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.   
Google GDPR compliance : https://privacy.google.com/businesses/ 

###### To whom we disclose your personal data

We may share Personal Data with the owner of intellectual property rights to the Website and software used on it and to the extent needed to perform certain business-related functions (e.g. updates, maintenance, support, etc.) for the purpose of providing Services to you.   
We may share Personal Data with entities that are controlled by or under common control with Offer18 (each, an “Affiliate”) for the purpose of assisting Offer18 in providing its Services to you. In that event, any such Affiliate will use Personal Data solely as permitted under this Policy.   
We may disclose Personal Data to public authorities if required to do so by law or to comply with a legal obligation. If we are requested by law to disclose any of your Personal Data, we will use reasonable efforts to provide you with notice of that disclosure requirement, unless we are prohibited from doing so by statute, court or administrative order.   
We reserve the right to sell, assign or transfer our business or assets. In any such event or similar event, including but not limiting to corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, etc., Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer or successor of Offer18 may continue to use your Personal Data as set forth in this Policy.   
Our employees have access to your Personal Data only to the extent their functions are required to provide our service or otherwise act on our behalf as set forth in this Policy. 

###### Security

We will maintain industry-standard physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect data in our possession from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. However, no method of transmission or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. We regularly test and update our technology to help protect your data. However, such precautions do not guarantee that our Website or the data stored during your use of the Services is invulnerable to hacking and will not be subject to a security breach. We make no warranty, guarantee, or representation that the Website or the Services are or will be protected from all viruses, security threats or other vulnerabilities or that your information will always be secure. 

###### Links to Other Sites

For the convenience of our visitors and clients, the Website may contain links to other sites, such as those of our partners or vendors, which are subject to different privacy policies. The Policy will not apply to your use of other websites. While we generally try to link only to sites that share similar high standards and respect for privacy, we have no responsibility or liability for the content, products or services offered, independent actions, or the privacy and security practices employed by these other independent sites. We encourage you to ask questions and review the applicable privacy policies found on such other websites, services and applications to understand how your information may be collected and used on these independent sites before disclosing information to third parties. 

###### Data storage period 

Personal Data will be stored for as long as the Personal Data is required to provide Services or requested Website functionality. Other types of Personal Data, which are not required for the provision of Services, shall be stored for a period of up to 1 year or until (if) consent is withdrawn or other data subject’s rights are exercised. In some cases, Personal Data may be stored for a period longer than indicated or despite withdrawal of consent or request to erase Personal Data, if storage of Personal Data is required in order to protect our or third parties’ legitimate interests. 

###### Minors

We will never knowingly collect any Personal Data and personal information about individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If Offer18 obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from our platform. 

###### Your Rights, Questions and Complaints

You have a right to request rectification of Personal Data in our database (including Contact and Billing Information that you have provided to us) by contacting us at support@offer18.com. If you delete Personal Data or it is erased under your request, we will only retain such copies of the information as are necessary for us to protect our or third parties’ legitimate interests, comply with governmental orders, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, or enforce any agreement you have entered into with us.   
In certain cases, you may have a right to restrict processing of your Personal Data or to object to processing of your Personal Data. These rights can be exercised by contacting us at support@offer18.com.   
In cases where processing of Personal Data is based on your consent, you have the right to refuse and revoke consent to the processing of your Personal Data by contacting us at support@offer18.com. Upon termination of processing of your Personal Data it can be difficult or impossible to provide Services to you. 

**Our data privacy dept. can be contacted by email at privacy@offer18.com.**
